Guide to the Jimenez Family Papers TAM.838
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Jimenez, Michael A. -- Military, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Memo Hq Camp McQuaide to CG, Ninth SvC, Fort Douglas, Utah and Memo MAJ re: Approval MAJ Request for Relief from Active Duty, 1945-08-31
  - Memo MAJ through Commanding Officer, Camp MacQuaide to Adjutant General, Washington, D.C. Forwarding MAJ Request for Relief from Active Duty, 1945-08-31
  - Letter from Commanding Officer to War Price & Rationing Board re: MAJ Permission to Subsist off the Army Post, 1945-08-31
  - Schedule of Collections War Department re: MAJ Field Rations, 1945-09-14
  - Special Order US Army Service Forces Camp McQuaide re: MAJ to Fort Ord, 1945-09-21
  - Special Order US Army Service Forces Camp McQuaide re: Amendment to MAJ to Fort Ord, 1945-09-21
  - Officers Clearance Certificate re: MAJ to Fort Ord, CA, 1945-09-21
  - Special Order US Army Service Forces Fort Ord re: MAJ leave to Moylan PA, 1945-09-21
  - Schedule of Collections War Department re: MAJ Travel Payment, 1945-09-13
  - MAJ Officers' Pay, Allowance and Mileage Voucher War Department and Allotment Discontinuance, circa 1945
  - MAJ Army Separation Qualification Record, 1945-11-15
  - MAJ US Army Certificate of Service at Ft. Ord Separation Center (Camp McQuaide, CA) and Military Record and Report of Separation Certificate of Service, 1945-11-15
  - MAJ Officer's Adjusted Service Rating Form (Draft and Final), circa 1945
  - Memorandum for OSS Personnel Leaving the Theater, circa 1945
- Jimenez, Michael A. -- World War II Photographs, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Jimenez, Michael A. -- Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives Documents, 1940-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - MAJ membership cards – Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, Inc. (ALBA), 1940-1942
  - Copy of ALBA Letter Soliciting Archival Materials; Note from MAJ to Danny Duncan Collum Summarizing Involvement in Spanish Civil War and World War II and Offering Information, 1989-03-28
  - Copy of Published Letter from Delores H. Gleaton, to "The Volunteer: Organ of Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade" (page 18, Vol V, Number 3, December 1983)
  - Sunday Democrat and Chronicle Upstate Magazine including "The Age of Idealism" (p. 5) and "When American Fought in Spain" (p. 8-15), 1983-04-10
  - Annotated photo of Bill Aalto, Irving Goff, Alex Kunslich and Antonio Morreno, undated
- Jimenez, Michael A. -- Military Post World War II, 1947-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - US War Office Presidential Commission re: MAJ Appointment as Captain 1945-05-17, 1947-06-27
  - Memo US War Department Adjutant General to MAJ re: Commission ('formal evidence of highest military rank"), 1947-06-30
  - Letter US Department of the Army to MAJ re: Request to Resign from Commission and Confirmation of Termination, 1954-01-08
  - Response to Request for Separation Documents / Information National Personnel Records Center, Copy of 1945-11-15 Military Record and Report of Separation Certificate of Service, and Copy of letter National Personnel Records Center to MAJ re: Missing Records, 1976-01-09
- Jimenez-Walton Correspondence, 1943-01-1943-03 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-01-01
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-01
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-01-13
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-01-29
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Possibly January 29, 1943
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-02-04
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-02-06
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, February or March 1943
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-02-07
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-02-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-02-11
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-02-15
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-02-18
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-02-19
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-02-27
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-03-06
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-03-09
  - John Jimenez to Mike Jimenez and Manuel Jimenez, Africa, 1943-03-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-03-12
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-03-13
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-03-15
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-03-15
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-03-19
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-03-23
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-03-25
  - Frank Walton (Mary's aunt) to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-03-28
- Jimenez-Walton Correspondence, 1943-04-1943-06 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-01
  - William McKee Walton to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-01
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-02
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-04-04
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-09
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-04-11
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-15
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-16
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-04-16
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-17-1943-04-24
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-22
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-04-22
  - Judith (Judy) Walton, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-23
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-24
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-26
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-04-29
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-04-30
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-05-03-1943-05-07
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-05-05
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-05-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-05-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-05-07
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-05-13
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-05-15
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-05-18
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-05-21
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-05-28-1943-05-29
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-06-04
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-06-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-06-15
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-06-21
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-06-29
- Jimenez-Walton Correspondence, 1943-07-1943-12 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Rose Foster Avery Walton, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-07-03
  - Rose Foster Avery Walton, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-07-03
  - Rose Foster Avery Walton, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-07-03
  - Rose Foster Avery Walton, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-07-03
  - Rose Foster Avery Walton, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-07-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-07-03-1943-07-04
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-07-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Manuel Jimenez, 1943-07-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to [Jimenez Family?], 1943-07-14
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-07-14-1943-07-18
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-07-22
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-07-28-1943-07-29
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-07-28
  - John Jimenez to Mike Jimenez, 1943-07-31
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-08-01
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-08-05
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-08-05
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-08-10
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-08-11
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-08-19
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-08-19
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Africa, 1943-08-23
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-08-30
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-09-01
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-09-02
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-09-03
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-09-05
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-09-06
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-09-08
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-09-08
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-09-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-09-19
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-09-19
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-09-26
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10-05
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10-08
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-10-11
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10-14
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-10-14
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10-22
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10-24
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-10-24
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-10-30
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-10-31
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-01
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-04
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-08
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-11-11
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-14
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-11-14
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-17
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-21
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-22
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-11-23
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-23-1943-11-24
  - Mary Jimenez and Others to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-26
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-11-28
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-12-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-12-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-12-10
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-12-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-12-12
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-12-12
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-12-19
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-12-19
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1943-12-25
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-12-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1943-12-29
- Jimenez-Walton Correspondence, 1944-01-1944-03 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-02
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-02
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-04
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-01-08
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-10
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-01-11
  - William McKee Walton to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-11
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-01-18
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-24
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-24
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-30
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-30
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-01-31
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-02-02
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-03
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-02-04
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-02-02
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-02-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-12
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-02-12
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-02-17
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-22
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-02-26
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-02-27
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-03-02
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-05
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-05
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-05
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-09
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-03-09
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-15
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-15
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-15
- Jimenez-Walton Correspondence, 1944-03-1944-06 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-03-17
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-22
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-22
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-22
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-03-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-30
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-30
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-03-30
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-30-1944-03-31
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-31
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-03-31
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-03
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-04-06
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-09
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-09
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-04-10
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-18
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-18
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-18
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-18
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-18
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-04-21
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-22-1944-04-23
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-23
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-04-23
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-05-01
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-01
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-01
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-05
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-05-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-11
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-11
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-11
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-05-13
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-05-15
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-05-19
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-24
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-05-27
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-05-30
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-06-03
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-06-06
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-06-13
- Jimenez-Walton Correspondence, 1944-06-1944-10 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mike Jimenez, Italy to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-06-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-06-14
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-06-16
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-06-19
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-06-26
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-06-28
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-07-01
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-07-01
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-07-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-07-08
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-07-08
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-07-08
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-07-13-1944-07-14
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-07-14
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-07-23
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-07-28-1944-07-30
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-07-28
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-08-07
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-08-12
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-08-17
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, Italy, 1944-08-24-1944-08-28
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-09-01
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, Possibly September 27, 1944
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-09-06
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-09-09
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-09-10
  - Mike Jimenez, Africa to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-09-13
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-09-13
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-09-17
  - Mike Jimenez, Italy to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-09-24
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-09-25
  - Mary Jimenez, Atlantic City to Mike Jimenez, 1944-09-30-1944-10-01
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-10-09
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-10-09
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-10-12
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-10-17
  - Mike Jimenez, Italy to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-10-18
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-10-22
  - Mike Jimenez, Italy to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-10-26
  - Mike Jimenez, Italy to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-10-31
- Jimenez-Walton Correspondence, 1944-11-1945-05 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1944-11-01
  - Mike Jimenez, Italy to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-11-07
  - Mike Jimenez, Italy to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-11-12
  - Mike Jimenez, Italy to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-11-18
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-12-07-1944-12-08
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-12-14
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1944-12-25
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-01-01-1945-01-03
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-01-11
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-01-17
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, France, 1945-01-29
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-02-08
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-02-14
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1945-02-17
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-02-21
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1945-03-07
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-03-16
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1945-03-16
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-03-19
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-03-25
  - Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA to Mike Jimenez, 1945-03-27
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-04-09
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-04-15
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-04-20
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-04-25
  - Mike Jimenez, France to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, 1945-05-02
  - Mike Jimenez to Mary Jimenez, Rose Valley, PA, Likely January 24, 1944
- Jimenez, Michael A. -- UA, IAM, and Other Employment and Activism, 1941-1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - MAJ 1956 UE (United Electrical Workers) Membership Card, 1955-12-27
  - Copy of Letter MAJ (Field Organizer UE) to Julius Emspak, Editor "UE News", 1942-01-08
  - Letter Julius Emspak UE General Secretary-Treasurer to MAJ re: Reinstatement Effective 1945-10-15, 1945-10-16
  - Flyer "The Record Speaks for Itself" re: MAJ, Daniel A. Fitzgerald and William E. Ward, circa 1946-1956
  - City Court Rome NY Certificate of Conviction for Assault in 3rd Degree on 1946-02-27, Discharged after Trial, 1946-03-07
  - Letter UE James J. Matles to MAJ re: Appointment as International Representative Effective 1948-07-01, 1948-07-06
  - Letter UE District Council 3 to MAJ re: District 3 Staff History, 1948-11-23
  - UE District 3 Staff List, 1945-10-01-1948-11-23
  - Letter UE Frances Sayler to MAJ, 1950-07-06
  - John C. Davies (D, N.Y.) 1949 Voting Record, 1950
  - John C. Davies (D, N.Y.) 1950 Voting Record
  - John C. Davies (D, N.Y.) Speeches and Insertions in the Record, 1950
  - Copy of Letter American Labor Party Candidate (ALP) Ross Maracchion to Congressman John C. Davies re: Refusal to Debate ALP, 1950-10-13
  - Letter Uniformed Firemen's Association to MAJ re: Support for Pay Raise in Fall 1950, 1951-02-17
  - Copy letter Rochester Ordnance Corps to MAJ re: Release of Cable from General Cable Corporation Plant for Defense Production, 1952-09-25
  - Letter Jean T. McKelvey NYS Board of Mediation Thanking MAJ and Transmitting Letter to UE, 1956-01-11